[
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"You guys are going to stand out like ___ thumb.",
			"optionA":"a sore",
			"optionB":"a swollen",
			"optionC":"bruised",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"My joke about the alcoholic went down like a lead ___.",
			"optionA":"ball",
			"optionB":"balloon",
			"optionC":"load",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"His father always smoked like a ___.",
			"optionA":"candle",
			"optionB":"pipe",
			"optionC":"chimney",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Our teacher at school used to have eyes like ____.",
			"optionA":"a hawk",
			"optionB":"an eagle",
			"optionC":"an owl",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"The country is safe as ___ for visitors.",
			"optionA":"flats",
			"optionB":"houses",
			"optionC":"blocks",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Physically John is as ___ as nails.",
			"optionA":"strong",
			"optionB":"solid",
			"optionC":"hard",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"The film was as ___ as dishwater and we decided to leave.",
			"optionA":"dull",
			"optionB":"grim",
			"optionC":"flat",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"We'll need to make sure the car is as ___ as a whistle",
			"optionA":"shiny",
			"optionB":"clean",
			"optionC":"bright",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Today I can't. I'm as busy as ___.",
			"optionA":"a bird",
			"optionB":"an ant",
			"optionC":"a bee",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"If you go to the gym everyday. You'll be as strong as ___.",
			"optionA":"an ox",
			"optionB":"a fox",
			"optionC":"a horse",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"That was a hard class. His explanation was as clear ___.",
			"optionA":"as clay",
			"optionB":"as mud",
			"optionC":"as sludge",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"For me, watching a soccer match is like watching grass ___.",
			"optionA":"go",
			"optionB":"flow",
			"optionC":"grow",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Don't just sit there like a bump on a ___.",
			"optionA":"log",
			"optionB":"fog",
			"optionC":"frog",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"She is tall and thin as a ___.",
			"optionA":"fake",
			"optionB":"rake",
			"optionC":"scrape",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"She walked in as cool ___, as if nothing had happened.",
			"optionA":"as lettuce",
			"optionB":"as an eggplant",
			"optionC":"as a cucumber",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	}
]